<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<privacyPolicy>
    <lastUpdated>15 April 2026</lastUpdated>

    <content><![CDATA[
# Privacy Policy

**Last updated:** 15 April 2026

AXT LIMITED, also trading as **AXT** (“we”, “us”, or “our”), is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how information is handled when you access or use our website, software, games, and related services (the “Services”).

We are based in **New Zealand** and design our data practices in accordance with generally accepted international privacy principles, including transparency, data minimisation, and purpose limitation.

---

## 1. Information We Collect

We collect **only limited information** required to operate our Services.

### 1.1 Account and Service Data

We store:
- Internal account identifiers
- Game or application statistics associated with those identifiers

This data **does not directly identify individuals** and does not include names, email addresses, billing details, or payment information.

### 1.2 Website Usage and Technical Data

When you visit our website, we may automatically collect:
- IP address
- Browser type and device information
- Pages visited and interactions
- Date and time of access
- Cookies or similar technologies

This data is used for analytics, performance monitoring, and security purposes.

### 1.3 Contact Information

If you contact us directly, we will collect:
- Your email address
- The content of your message
- Any information you choose to include

This information is stored within **Microsoft‑hosted email systems** and used only for communication and support purposes.

---

## 2. Information We Do Not Collect

We do not:
- Collect personal profiles or real‑world identity information through our Services
- Store payment or financial information
- Access or store login credentials for third‑party platforms
- Collect sensitive personal data

---

## 3. Third‑Party Services

Some aspects of our Services rely on third‑party providers.

### 3.1 Steam (Valve Corporation)

- Steam manages user accounts, authentication, purchases, and transactions
- We do not receive or access your personal Steam account information
- Steam’s data handling is governed by Steam’s own privacy policies

### 3.2 Website and Infrastructure Providers

- Hosting, analytics, and security providers may process technical data on our behalf
- These providers are required to protect data and use it only for authorised purposes

---

## 4. How We Use Information

Information is used to:
- Operate and maintain the Services
- Track gameplay or application statistics
- Improve functionality, stability, and security
- Monitor website usage and performance
- Respond to user enquiries
- Comply with legal and regulatory obligations

---

## 5. Cookies and Similar Technologies

We use cookies or similar technologies to:
- Analyse website traffic
- Improve user experience
- Maintain site functionality

You may control cookies through your browser settings. Disabling cookies may affect certain features.

---

## 6. Data Storage and Security

We implement reasonable technical and organisational safeguards to protect information against:
- Unauthorised access
- Loss or misuse
- Unauthorised disclosure or alteration

No method of electronic storage or transmission is completely secure, and absolute security cannot be guaranteed.

---

## 7. Data Retention

We retain information only for as long as necessary to:
- Provide and support the Services
- Meet legal, regulatory, or operational requirements

Data is deleted or anonymised when no longer required.

---

## 8. International Data Processing

Although we operate from New Zealand, some data may be processed or stored in other countries by third‑party service providers. Where this occurs, we take reasonable steps to ensure appropriate data protection safeguards are in place.

---

## 9. Your Rights

Depending on your location, you may have the right to:
- Request access to personal information we hold about you
- Request correction of inaccurate information
- Request deletion of information where applicable
- Object to or restrict certain processing

Requests can be made using the contact details below.

---

## 10. Children’s Privacy

Our Services are not intended for individuals under the age of 13 (or higher age thresholds where required by local law). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.

---

## 11. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy periodically. Updates will be posted on this page with a revised “Last updated” date. Continued use of the Services indicates acceptance of the updated policy.

---

## 12. Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or our data practices, you can contact us at:

**AXT LIMITED**  
Email: **contact@axt.co.nz**  
Country of operation: **New Zealand**
    ]]></content>
</privacyPolicy>
